city-visitor.com 2016-05-15

# Privacy Policy | Cityvisitor

Cityvisitor.co.uk is owned and operated by [Infoserve Ltd](http://www.infoserve.com/) (“Infoserve/we”).

Infoserve places great importance in protecting and respecting your privacy. This statement explains our policy towards your personal data and how we will treat it.

This policy applies whether or not you choose to take a listing on cityvisitor.co.uk.

## Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following information about you:

Information that you provide us with by completing forms on our website, for example information provided at the time of registering to use our website, purchasing our services, requesting a free listing or posting material on to our website.

We may also collect anonymous information on your browsing activity whilst logged on to our website, such as IP address, browser type, access times and referring URL.

## What we use this information for

We use the information held about you in the following ways:

To help us to understand your needs and improve the relevance of the services we offer you as an individual

To provide you with information (either by telephone, email, post or any other method), products of services that you request from us or which we feel may be of interest to you.

To carry out our obligations arising from any contract that you have entered into with us.

To allow you to fully participate in all the features of our website.

To keep you up to date about any changes to our services.

## Personal Information

In terms of the personal information you submit when becoming a user or an advertiser of cityvisitor.co.uk, this is held with the utmost commitment to your privacy.

The information is stored on a secure webserver and in accordance with the UK Data Protection Act 1998, we have added security measures in place to ensure that your personal information has adequate protection. This not only applies to your contact details but your credit/debit card details as well.

When payments are made to cityvisitor.co.uk, we regard security and convenience as top priorities and we only use established and secure methods such as Barclaycard EPDQ and CardStream.

If you use a web based payment page to pay for your listing, the credit/debit card details you submit are encapsulated using Barclaycard EPDQ's encrypted and digitally-signed protocol. This is done using Secure Socket Layer (SSL), the industry standard for transmitting confidential information on the web using data encryption, ensuring that the information passed on to us is secure and tamper-proof. However SSL has been designed to work with most popular browsers and you are advised to use an up to date version of your browser to take advantage of this added security.

We believe that your privacy is important and have security in place to protect it. However if this security is breeched we cannot guarantee the security of your information.

## Public Information

Listings information submitted for display on the cityvisitor.co.uk website is information for the public domain and therefore cannot be classed as private. If we request any information which could be classed as private, Infoserve will make you aware of this at the time of submission.

By submitting your listings information to cityvisitor.co.uk, you give Infoserve Ltd unconditional permission to use this information regardless of any moral rights, copyright, service mark, trademark or patent laws. Further you allow Infoserve Ltd to publish, modify, edit, translate, distribute and otherwise reproduce the information in whatever format we choose.

## Browsing our website

You cannot be identified personally as a result of the information we collect while you browse the site and we mainly examine browsing activity to monitor aggregated site traffic and analyse it.

We may also provide anonymous statistics about user's browsing activity to reputable third party vendors, but these will not include details that would allow the recipient to identify you.

## Cookies

Information About Our Use of Cookies

Infoserve uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our websites. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our websites and also allows us to improve our sites. By continuing to browse our sites, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers chosen by each website. Your browser stores these cookies and returns them when you revisit that website.

We use the following cookies:

  * **Strictly necessary cookies.** These are cookies that are required for the operation of our websites. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a shopping cart or make use of e-billing services.
  * **Analytical/performance cookies.** They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our websites. This helps us to improve the way our websites work, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.
  * **Functionality cookies.** These are used to recognise you when you return to our websites. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).
  * **Targeting cookies.** These cookies record your visit to our websites, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our websites and the advertising displayed on them more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.

Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies.

You may block cookies by activating the setting on your browser or device that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our sites.

## Third party links

Cityvisitor.co.uk contains links to other sites but we cannot assume responsibility for any other site's content or information handling practices. We urge you to review each site's privacy policy before entering into transactions with them.

## Telephone calls with Infoserve Ltd

Please note that calls with Infoserve may be monitored and recorded.

## Your Consent

By advertising on, or using this website, you agree that you are happy for your information to be gathered and used in the ways described in this policy.

However, if you change your mind about the way you have agreed your data can be used, just contact us via the website to stop specific or all uses of your data

All data collected by Infoserve Limited is shared with our data provider for verification and use in their marketing files.
